admost.com 2019-06-28

# Privacy Policy - Admost

We are updating our Privacy Policy which clarifies the details of personal data usage in accordance with privacy protection. We will share personal data, which is collected via the website or taken by Admost services, only in the ways described in this privacy policy. We do not sell any personal data to Third Parties.

Admost collects personal data in order to provide the services or business purposes, please note that you are not required by law to provide Admost with any personal data. This Privacy Policy explains working principle of Admost and which information get through the system. The terms “Admost”, “we”, “our” and “us” include Admost Mediation Limited and any affiliates and subsidiaries.

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. In the event of any material changes, there will be a post of new Privacy Policy on the website. We encourage you for consulting this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.

### **1\. Admost Services**

Admost is a tool that optimizes ad revenues and gives analytical information for mobile apps.

**Mediation** service working principle work through integrating Admost Software Development Kit to mobile app; to send requests and get ads over Admost Mediation Router which are provided by ad networks.

**Analytics** service gives analytical data of mobile apps to publishers. Analytics service gives details of user behavior to a publisher for improving mobile app performance and retention rate.

### **2\. Personal Data Collected by Admost via Web Site**

Registration Information: Admost website collects information as name, email, phone number, company name and app/game link for completing the signing up process. Admost may use your information for its business purposes; to contact you, for support services and, for marketing purposes.

You can subscribe for newsletter services preferably, thereafter you have an option to unsubscribe. 

Also, our employees are sworn to confidentiality.

### **3\. Subsidiary Tools for Admost Web Site**

Admost website utilizes a service of Google Analytics which collects information as device/browser, IP address and on-site/app activities to measure and report statistics about user interactions on the websites and/or apps anonymously.

You can find more details in http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html for Google

Analytics Services and you can opt out by going to [http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

You can find details of other tools that we use as the subsidiary for the website: 

### **4\. Admost may share personal data**

  * When required by law or regulation
  * To protect our rights or preserve the safety of our users
  * If required to investigate fraud; may include exchanging information with other companies and organizations.
  * Situation of Merger & Acquisition, Sale of All or Portion of Assets: In the event of thistype of situation your personal data will be shared under the appropriate confidentiality and only for purposes which you approved in the first place.

You should be aware that the information submitted to public areas, such as blogs, may be used by others.

### **5\. Accessing your personal data**

You may contact us and request to access the personal data that Admost keeps by emailing privacy@admost.com. There will be some requisites to make sure that you are the owner of the account.

If you want to delete data that you have provided or withdraw your consent, please contact us by privacy@admost.com and Admost will respond within a reasonable time after receiving your email.

After your deletion request put into the process, it will be deleted on Admost active servers immediately but deletion on backup systems will occur in 7 days. Also, you should be aware of that deletion cannot retrieve or delete personal data which has been already shared with partners and other Third Parties.

Please be aware that your personal data can be used by Admost to comply with legal obligations and Admost’ s agreements.

### **6\. Mediation & Analytics as Services**

Mediation provides service to publishers. To activate publisher account, Admost needs information for registration and completing the setup process which may be collected by the website.

Account information includes name, company name, telephone number, and email. If you are not volunteering to share this information with Admost, you may choose to send mail to amr@admost.com. For payment process, Admost needs billing information which keeps in a secure system within the company.

For providing our services as mediation, publishers should integrate a software development kit (SDK) to their mobile applications. Admost collects information about end users of mobile applications through SDK, including Advertising IDs (IDFA), usage statistics such as session, duration, impression, and click-throughs.

Mediation service provides ads for publisher via ad networks. System informs publisher about which ad networks will be integrated to their mobile application. Publishers agree that for using Admost SDK, they should get appropriate consent from their users for using and sharing of personal data through Admost SDK. It is important to take consent from users which should be compatible with laws and regulations for the country that your mobile application users are located.

Ad networks as ad providers send targeted ads that associated with end-users point of interest with the help of Mobile Advertising ID which can be considered as personal data. End users have an option to limit the access Advertising ID (IDFA) for ad targeting on your devices.

  * For iOS devices: Settings > Privacy > Advertising > Limit Ad Tracking.
  * For Android devices: Google Settings > Ads > Opt Out of Interest-Based Ads. Another option is to reset the Advertising ID (IDFA) on your mobile device.
  * For iOS Devices: Settings > Privacy > Advertising > Reset Advertising Identifier.
  * For Android: Google settings > Ads > Reset advertising ID.

Such a fresh start makes harder to associate with your past activity, but tracking will continue as a new user.

Mediation service has a reporting feature for publishers to have information about ad/revenue performance. Reports include information as geographic and demographic which are de-identified information. This type of information is not Personal Data and helps analyze revenue distribution based on the country to help publishers for improving their businesses.

Publishers may submit voluntarily their Advertising ID for adding testers for test process.

Analytics service provides analysis of user experience for publishers. Admost collects information about end users of mobile applications through SDK, including Advertising IDs (IDFA), usage statistics such as session, duration, impression, and click-throughs and create aggregated and anonymous information. The analytics report provided by Admost includes; user acquisition, session information, cohort analysis, retention analysis and in-app purchases.

Publishers have an option for not giving consent for collecting Advertising IDs (IDFA) of their mobile apps’ users. Collecting Advertising IDs may vary depending on the location of users according to laws and regulations. If there are constraints for collecting Advertising IDs as personal data, the default option will be not collecting Advertising IDs.

### **7\. GDPR Rights for EU people**

General Data Protection Regulation imposes a restriction for using personal data without getting the consent of EEA and Switzerland users.

_GDPR Terminology_

_Data subject: A data subject is a natural person. Examples of a data subject can be an individual, a customer, a prospect, an employee, a contact person, etc._

_Personal data: Any information relating to an identified / identifiable individual, whether it relates to his or her private, professional, or public life. Can be anything from a name, photo, email address, bank details, posts on social networking sites, medical information, IP address, or a combination of the data that directly or indirectly identifies the person._

_Data controller: Any organization, person, or body that determines the purposes and means of processing personal data, controls the data and is responsible for it, alone or jointly. Examples of the data controller is an individual include general practitioners, pharmacists, and politicians, where these individuals keep personal information about their patients, clients, constituents etc. Examples of organizations can be data controllers, for profit or not for profit, private or government-owned, large or small, where those organizations keep personal information about their employees, clients, etc._

_Data processor: A data processor processes the data on behalf of the data controller. Examples include payroll companies, accountants, and market research companies._

_Processing: Processing is an operation performed on personal data (sets), such as creation, collection, storage, view, transport, use, modification, transfer, deletion, etc., whether or not by automated means._

_EEA Countries: Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Great Britain, Greece, Holland, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden._

_Also, Switzerland is GDPR applicable country._

For the website, Admost processes data as controller and adapting website fully compatible with GDPR.

For Mediation and Analytics services, publishers who provide service in GDPR applicable areas should admit the responsibility for taking consent to collect personal data of users.

As EEA and Switzerland residents, you have options indicated below:

  * You can access data that Admost and ad networks partners keep about you. There will be some requisites to make sure that you are the owner of the account. You may change data in case of any inaccurate, outdated or missing data and provide us with the necessary information to set aright it.
  * You can withdraw your consent if you do not want your personal data to continue to be processed. Exercising this right will not affect the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.
  * You can request delete or restrict access to your personal data. If your personal data is in current use for providing services or legitimate purposes, your request may be postponed or get rejected. After your deletion request put into the process, it will be deleted on Admost active servers immediately but deletion on backup systems will occur in 7 days.

You may request to be informed for actions that Third Parties do with your personal data.

You have the right to have the personal data transmitted directly from one controller to another, where technically feasible (Art 20 para 2). You have the right to object at any time to the processing of personal data concerning you for such marketing, which includes profiling to the extent that it is related to such direct marketing (Art 21 para 2). You have the right not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling, which produces legal effects concerning or significantly affects you (Art. 22 para 1). You have a right to lodge a complaint with a data protection supervisory authority. (Art. 77 para 1) 

Admost is the data processor for your Advertising ID  data.

IDFA-like data used by Admost; Companies like Apple, Google, etc. are the pseudonymous data created for targeted advertising purposes. Here is how you will use your rights of disposition on this data. This data will be processed for targeted advertising, without matching your other personal data.

Pseudonymisation is recognized as a safeguard that reduces the risks to data subjects and helps controllers and processors meet their data protection obligations. If you have any concerns, please do not hesitate to contact Admost at privacy@admost.com.

### **8\. Data Retention**

Admost retains the information about you for as long as you use Admost services or as necessary for business purposes or required by legal obligations. Unless you request to delete your information or required by law, Admost will keep information about you for active accounts.

For accounts that do not have any action for 180 days, information will be deleted from Admost system.

### **9\. Children**

Admost do not knowingly collect, maintain or use personal data from children under the age of 13 (and in certain jurisdictions under the age of 16) or from websites or online services directed to children under the age of 13 (and in certain jurisdictions under the age of 16). In the unlikely event, as a parent or legal guardian of a child, you may alert us privacy@admost.com to have your child’s personal data deleted.

### **10\. Information Security**

The security of your personal and non-personal data is important to us. Admost takes necessary precaution and security standards to protect your personal data. We encrypt your personal data to prevent unauthorized access, damage, expose or use of information.

Please be aware that Admost cannot guarantee the security of any information you provide to us. Although we take all precautions to provide security of your personal data, we do not promise that your personal data will always be in secure. In the event of any security flaw, you will be noticed by website or an email.

### **11\. Data Transfer**

We may share your information as described in this Privacy Policy (with ad networks as our Third-Party service providers, when required by law, to protect our rights or preserve the safety of our users) or with your consent.

The complete ad network list as Third-Party service provider list can be found here:

  * Admob
  * Facebook
  * One by AOL
  * Adcolony
  * Flurry
  * Pollfish
  * Adtiming
  * Fyber
  * Startapp
  * Adview
  * Double Click Ad Exchange
  * IronSource
  * Amazon
  * Inmobi
  * Tapjoy
  * Applovin
  * Inneractive
  * UnityAds
  * Appnext
  * LoopMe
  * Smaato
  * Avocarrot/Glispa
  * Mobfox
  * Vungle
  * Chartboost
  * Mopub
  * YouAppi

### **12\. California Privacy Rights**

For California residents, California law permits users to request the list of relating Third Parties to which Admost has disclosed personal information for direct marketing purposes during the preceding year.

Admost does not share Personal Information with Third Parties for their own marketing purposes.

### **13\. Our right to change the guidelines without prior notice**

We reserve the right to change these guidelines at any time, taking into account all applicable privacy protection laws.

### **14\. Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@admost.com.
